export const quizQuestions_1 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: "What is the primary purpose of functional components in React?",
      choices: [
        "Manage component state",
        "Handle component lifecycle methods",
        "Reusable building blocks with UI logic",
        "Access external APIs"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Reusable building blocks with UI logic"
    },
    {
      question: "How do you pass data from a parent component to a child component in React?",
      choices: [
        "Using component refs",
        "Via component state",
        "Through props",
        "By using the Redux store"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Through props"
    },
    {
      question: "In a functional component, how do you access the props passed to it?",
      choices: [
        "this.props",
        "props",
        "state.props",
        "props.data"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "props"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the function of the useState hook in React?",
      choices: [
        "Accessing the component's state",
        "Declaring a new state variable",
        "Initializing component props",
        "Defining component lifecycle methods"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Declaring a new state variable"
    },
    {
      question: "When does the componentDidMount lifecycle method get called?",
      choices: [
        "Before the component renders",
        "After the component renders",
        "During the component's unmounting",
        "Only once, after the initial render"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Only once, after the initial render"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the correct way to update the state in a functional component?",
      choices: [
        "this.setState({})",
        "setState({})",
        "setNewState({})",
        "updateState({})"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "setState({})"
    },
    {
      question: "How do you import a default export from a module?",
      choices: [
        "import default from 'module';",
        "import { default } from 'module';",
        "import * as default from 'module';",
        "import 'module' as default;"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "import default from 'module';"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the purpose of the export default statement in a module?",
      choices: [
        "It exports all named exports from the module.",
        "It is used to import the default export in another module.",
        "It marks the module as the main entry point for an application.",
        "It defines a default value or function to be exported."
      ],
      correctAnswer: "It defines a default value or function to be exported."
    },
    {
      question: "How do you perform a ternary operation in JavaScript?",
      choices: [
        "if (condition) {...} else {...}",
        "condition ? true : false",
        "switch (condition) {...}",
        "condition ? {...} : {...}"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "condition ? true : false"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the purpose of short-circuiting in JavaScript?",
      choices: [
        "Skipping unnecessary code execution based on a condition",
        "Reducing the size of the code",
        "Minimizing the time complexity of the code",
        "Preventing code from running in the browser console"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Skipping unnecessary code execution based on a condition"
    },
    {
      question: "Which syntax is used for array destructuring in JavaScript?",
      choices: [
        "{}",
        "[]",
        "()",
        "<>"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "[]"
    },
    {
      question: "What does the spread operator (...) do in JavaScript?",
      choices: [
        "Combines two arrays into one",
        "Copies the properties of one object into another",
        "Multiplies the elements of an array",
        "Executes a function multiple times"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Copies the properties of one object into another"
    },
  ],
    }
  